In the Name of the King III is a action, adventure,
drama film directed by Uwe Boll.
Hazen Kaine, an American contract killer living in Sofia, Bulgaria, gets more
than he bargains for when he enters into a contract with the mob.
One last job before he gets out and starts a new life for himself.
The targets: the three children of royal billionaire Andon Dupont.
Seems simple enough, or so he thought.
Hazen apprehends the children, and before he can blink an eye, a simple necklace worn
by one of the children sends his life spiraling back to medieval times.
Now completely out of his element, Hazen fights for his life as he tries to
escape a medieval army and a fierce fire-breathing dragon.
Hazen Kaine, played by Dominic Purcell.
Arabella, played by Ralitsa Paskaleva.
Emeline, played by Daria Simeonova.
Sophie, played by Petra Gocheva.
Alys, played by Marina Dakova.
Ulrich, played by Bashar Rahal.
In the Name of the King: A Dungeon Siege Tale (also known as Dungeon Siege: In the Name of the King or simply In the Name of the King) is a 2007 English-language fantasy action film
directed by Uwe Boll and starring Jason Statham, Claire Forlani, Leelee Sobieski, John Rhys-Davies, Ron Perlman, Ray Liotta and Burt Reynolds with Kristanna Loken.
It is inspired by the Dungeon Siege video game series, and was an international
co-production between Germany, Canada, and the United States.
It premiered at the Brussels Festival of Fantastic Films on April 11,
2007, and was released in theatres on November 29, 2007.
Upon its release, the film was a critical and commercial failure,
grossing only $13.1 million against a budget of $60 million.
The film explores themes of medallion, mercenary,
dragon, based on video game, sisters.
The tone is emotional.